<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss  xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" 
      xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
      xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" 
      xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" 
      version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Kundan Kumar</title>
<link>https://kundan-kumarr.github.io/talks.html</link>
<atom:link href="https://kundan-kumarr.github.io/talks.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
<description>Talks, invited lectures, and presentations.</description>
<generator>quarto-1.7.33</generator>
<lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 05:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
<item>
  <title>Scaling Smart Grids with Transfer Learning and DRL</title>
  <dc:creator>Kundan Kumar</dc:creator>
  <link>https://kundan-kumarr.github.io/talks/pes_gm_2025/</link>
  <description><![CDATA[ 




<section id="introduction" class="level2">
<h2 class="anchored" data-anchor-id="introduction">Introduction</h2>
<p>As renewable energy integration accelerates, modern power grids face mounting complexity in maintaining stability and efficiency. Deep Reinforcement Learning (DRL) has emerged as a powerful technique for <strong>Volt-Var Control (VVC)</strong> — regulating voltage levels across the distribution grid — but its Achilles’ heel lies in <strong>expensive retraining</strong>.<br>
Every new grid topology or environment demands retraining from scratch, costing time, data, and computational energy.</p>
<p>In our latest work, presented at the <em>Workshop on Autonomous Energy Systems (GRID-EDGE 2025)</em>, we introduce a <strong>Transfer Learning (TL)-based DRL framework</strong> that enables policy reuse across different grid configurations — cutting training time by <em>98.14%</em> while improving performance by <em>69.51%</em>.</p>
<hr>
</section>
<section id="core-idea-transfer-learning-meets-drl" class="level2">
<h2 class="anchored" data-anchor-id="core-idea-transfer-learning-meets-drl">Core Idea: Transfer Learning Meets DRL</h2>
<p>Traditional DRL systems learn from scratch. TL-DRL systems, however, <strong>transfer policy knowledge</strong> from a source grid (e.g., IEEE-123 Bus) to a target grid (e.g., IEEE-13 Bus).</p>
<p><img src="https://kundan-kumarr.github.io/talks/pes_gm_2025/image_talk_20220616.png" class="img-fluid" style="width:60.0%"></p>
<p>This approach allows agents to <strong>start smarter</strong>, building upon previously learned representations rather than reinventing them. The heart of this system is a <strong>policy reuse classifier</strong>, a small neural network that decides when the previously learned policy should be reused or adapted.</p>
<hr>
</section>
<section id="how-it-works" class="level2">
<h2 class="anchored" data-anchor-id="how-it-works">How It Works</h2>
<p>The framework operates in three phases:</p>
<section id="source-training" class="level3">
<h3 class="anchored" data-anchor-id="source-training">1. <strong>Source Training</strong></h3>
<p>A DRL agent, using the Proximal Policy Optimization (PPO) algorithm, learns to manage the IEEE-123 Bus system. The policy parameters, denoted as θₛₒᵤᵣcₑ, optimize voltage levels and reactive power flow according to ANSI C84.1-2020 voltage standards.</p>
</section>
<section id="policy-reuse-classifier" class="level3">
<h3 class="anchored" data-anchor-id="policy-reuse-classifier">2. <strong>Policy Reuse Classifier</strong></h3>
<p>We train a binary classifier that predicts the probability of reusing a learned policy: [ P(|) = (f_()) ] If this probability exceeds 0.5, the source policy is transferred directly; otherwise, the agent retrains in the target environment.</p>
</section>
<section id="target-adaptation" class="level3">
<h3 class="anchored" data-anchor-id="target-adaptation">3. <strong>Target Adaptation</strong></h3>
<p>The target model (θₜₐᵣgₑₜ) adapts to the IEEE-13 Bus through <strong>fine-tuning and Q-value updates</strong>, balancing exploration and exploitation dynamically: [ = P(|) ] This adaptive mechanism allows the agent to decide when to trust previous experience and when to explore new strategies.</p>
<hr>
</section>
</section>
<section id="experimental-setup" class="level2">
<h2 class="anchored" data-anchor-id="experimental-setup">Experimental Setup</h2>
<p>We implemented the system in <strong>OpenDSS</strong> using the <strong>PowerGym</strong> RL environment.<br>
The source policy (IEEE-123 Bus) was trained for 20,000 iterations, taking 313 seconds.<br>
The TL-enhanced target model (IEEE-13 Bus) adapted in just <strong>9.6 seconds</strong> — compared to <strong>518 seconds</strong> when trained from scratch.</p>
<table class="caption-top table">
<thead>
<tr class="header">
<th>Metric</th>
<th>Training with TL</th>
<th>Without TL</th>
</tr>
</thead>
<tbody>
<tr class="odd">
<td>Mean Reward</td>
<td>-8.310</td>
<td>-27.256</td>
</tr>
<tr class="even">
<td>Training Time</td>
<td>9.62 s</td>
<td>518.38 s</td>
</tr>
<tr class="odd">
<td>T-Statistic</td>
<td>102.93</td>
<td>—</td>
</tr>
<tr class="even">
<td>P-Value</td>
<td>6.38</td>
<td>—</td>
</tr>
<tr class="odd">
<td>TAS (Task Adaptation Score)</td>
<td>72.78</td>
<td>—</td>
</tr>
<tr class="even">
<td>Embedding Distance (ED)</td>
<td>31.11</td>
<td>—</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
<p>These results show that TL not only speeds up convergence but also produces a <strong>statistically significant performance improvement</strong>.</p>
<hr>
</section>
<section id="key-insights" class="level2">
<h2 class="anchored" data-anchor-id="key-insights">Key Insights</h2>
<ol type="1">
<li><strong>Efficiency Leap</strong> — TL cut training time by 98%, accelerating grid simulation workflows dramatically.<br>
</li>
<li><strong>Policy Robustness</strong> — The classifier effectively distinguished when to reuse policies, preserving stability in unseen grid configurations.<br>
</li>
<li><strong>Scalability</strong> — The approach generalizes across systems of different complexity, paving the way for large-scale adaptive control.</li>
</ol>
<hr>
</section>
<section id="broader-impact" class="level2">
<h2 class="anchored" data-anchor-id="broader-impact">Broader Impact</h2>
<p>The proposed <strong>TL-DRL framework</strong> makes reinforcement learning practical for real-world grid management.<br>
By leveraging existing knowledge, utilities can deploy <strong>smarter and faster control policies</strong>, reducing both <strong>operational costs</strong> and <strong>computational footprints</strong> — a critical step toward <strong>sustainable AI-driven power systems</strong>.</p>
<hr>
</section>
<section id="whats-next" class="level2">
<h2 class="anchored" data-anchor-id="whats-next">What’s Next</h2>
<p>Our next goal is to <strong>scale TL across multiple grid sizes</strong> — from micro-grids to regional networks — and to integrate <strong>physics-informed constraints</strong> that further improve generalization.<br>
We also aim to extend this framework to <strong>federated and collaborative learning</strong> paradigms, allowing distributed grids to share intelligence securely.</p>
<hr>
</section>
<section id="reference" class="level2">
<h2 class="anchored" data-anchor-id="reference">Reference</h2>
<p>Kundan Kumar, Ravikumar Gelli.<br>
<strong>“Transfer Learning Enhanced Deep Reinforcement Learning for Volt-Var Control in Smart Grids.”</strong><br>
Workshop on Autonomous Energy Systems, GRID-EDGE 2025.</p>
<p>We developed a TL-DRL framework, as shown in Fig.~<img src="https://latex.codecogs.com/png.latex?%5Cref%7Bfig:A2C%7D">, which involves transferring policy knowledge from one distribution grid to another. Additionally, we have created a policy reuse classifier to determine whether to transfer the policy knowledge from the IEEE-123 Bus to the IEEE-13 Bus system and conducted an impact analysis.</p>
<p><img src="https://kundan-kumarr.github.io/talks/pes_gm_2025/image_talk_20220616.png" class="img-fluid" style="width:60.0%"></p>
</section>
<section id="about-the-talk" class="level2">
<h2 class="anchored" data-anchor-id="about-the-talk">About the talk</h2>
<p>We developed a TL-DRL framework, as shown in Fig.~<img src="https://latex.codecogs.com/png.latex?%5Cref%7Bfig:A2C%7D">, which involves transferring policy knowledge from one distribution grid to another. Additionally, we have created a policy reuse classifier to determine whether to transfer the policy knowledge from the IEEE-123 Bus to the IEEE-13 Bus system and conducted an impact analysis. <img src="https://latex.codecogs.com/png.latex?%5Cbegin%7Bequation%7D%5Clabel%7Beq:ppo_objective%7D%0A%5Ctheta_%7B%5Ctext%7Bsource%7D%7D%20=%20%5Carg%20%5Cmax_%7B%5Ctheta%7D%20%5Cmathbb%7BE%7D_%7B%5Ctau%20%5Csim%20%5Cpi_%7B%5Ctheta%7D%7D%20%5Cleft%5B%20%5Csum_%7Bt=0%7D%5E%7BT%7D%20%5Cgamma%5Et%20r_t%20-%20%5Cbeta%20%5Ctext%7BCLIP%7D(%5Ctheta)%20%5Cright%5D%0A%5Cend%7Bequation%7D"> The <img src="https://latex.codecogs.com/png.latex?%5Ctheta_%7B%5Ctext%7Bsource%7D%7D"> is trained with the DRL algorithm on the IEEE-123 Bus, which regulates the VVC voltage profiles within permissible limits.</p>
<p>While <img src="https://latex.codecogs.com/png.latex?%5Ctheta_%7B%5Ctext%7Btarget%7D%7D"> is the model which transferred the knowledge <img src="https://latex.codecogs.com/png.latex?%5Ctheta_%7B%5Ctext%7Bsource%7D%7D"> and adapts well in the <img src="https://latex.codecogs.com/png.latex?%5Ctheta_%7B%5Ctext%7Btarget%7D%7D"> domain. <img src="https://latex.codecogs.com/png.latex?%5Cbegin%7Bequation%7D%5Clabel%7Beq:target_theta%7D%0A%5Ctheta_%7B%5Ctext%7Btarget%7D%7D%20=%0A%5Cbegin%7Bcases%7D%0A%5Cbegin%7Baligned%7D%0A%5Ctheta_%7B%5Ctext%7Bsource%7D%7D%5C;%20&amp;%20%5Ctext%7Bif%20%7D%20P(%5Ctext%7BReuse%7D%7C%5Ctext%7BObservation%7D)%20%3E%200.5%0A%5Cend%7Baligned%7D%20%5C%5C%0A%5Carg%20%5Cmax_%7B%5Ctheta%7D%20%5Cmathbb%7BE%7D_%7B%5Ctau%20%5Csim%20%5Cpi_%7B%5Ctheta%7D%7D%20%5Cleft%5B%20%5Csum_%7Bt=0%7D%5E%7BT%7D%20%5Cgamma%5Et%20r_t%20%5Cright%5D%20&amp;%20%5Ctext%7Botherwise%7D%0A%5Cend%7Bcases%7D%0A%5Cend%7Bequation%7D"></p>



</section>

 ]]></description>
  <category>Smart Grids</category>
  <category>Reinforcement Learning</category>
  <category>Transfer Learning</category>
  <category>AI Research</category>
  <category>Energy Systems</category>
  <guid>https://kundan-kumarr.github.io/talks/pes_gm_2025/</guid>
  <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  <media:content url="https://kundan-kumarr.github.io/talks/pes_gm_2025/image_talk_20220616.png" medium="image" type="image/png" height="121" width="144"/>
</item>
<item>
  <title>Use Quarto, Make Friends</title>
  <link>https://kundan-kumarr.github.io/talks/community_20240921_quartofriends/</link>
  <description><![CDATA[ 




<p>It has been two years since Quarto became the most popular reproducible publication tool in data science and R community. However Quarto is so much more than just a publication tool! I started using it since late 2022, and it has helped me become more organized, productive and connected with people in the data science community.</p>
<p>In this talk I will not focus on the technical aspects on ‘how’ to use this tool. In the first part of the talk, I would like to report the latest news and trends seen in the useR conference and Posit conf, the two biggest global R events. In the second part, I will share my own experience in using Quarto for my career: from learning new skills, collaborating with co-workers, teaching university courses to networking and building a community (CAMIS collaboration). It is a powerful tool to share your work, and make new connections - both for work and for fun! I hope this talk will provide you with some new ideas on how to use this fantastic technology to fulfill your goals.</p>
<div class="quarto-video ratio ratio-16x9"><iframe data-external="1" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/0TEdFZ17FhY" title="" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></div>




 ]]></description>
  <category>Community</category>
  <category>Quarto</category>
  <guid>https://kundan-kumarr.github.io/talks/community_20240921_quartofriends/</guid>
  <pubDate>Sat, 21 Sep 2024 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
  <title>One step closer to better Electronic Health Records data</title>
  <link>https://kundan-kumarr.github.io/talks/ehr_20240918_betterehr/</link>
  <description><![CDATA[ 




<p>Real-World Data (RWD) like Electronic Health Records (EHR) is crucial for understanding drug usage and various treatments and generating Real-World Evidence (RWE). Risk prediction has been a major application where EHR is used, and there is now a shift towards causal inference, which requires data of even higher quality. Patients undergo treatments (drugs, procedures) at various times during their hospital stays, yet the data being recorded are messy and error-prone for various reasons. Analysts spend significant amount of time to sit together with clinicians to identify and understand abnormal records, and unfortunately this process is challenging to automate.</p>
<p>This talk will use an example on antibiotics prescription and use at a Nordic hospital to illustrate how some EHR systems can improve for better clinical decision-making and better data for research. I will also introduce a pilot R package (ggehr) that facilitates visual exploration of EHR data, and how it can help reconstruct patient journeys and enable analysts to perform effective quality control.</p>
<p><img src="https://kundan-kumarr.github.io/talks/ehr_20240918_betterehr/image_talk_20240918.png" class="img-fluid"></p>




 ]]></description>
  <category>RWD-EHR</category>
  <guid>https://kundan-kumarr.github.io/talks/ehr_20240918_betterehr/</guid>
  <pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
  <title>CAMIS: An Open-Source, Community endeavour for Comparing Analysis Method Implementations</title>
  <link>https://kundan-kumarr.github.io/talks/community_20240710_camis/</link>
  <description><![CDATA[ 




<p>2024.7.8-11, Salzburg, Austria. Conference link: <a href="https://events.linuxfoundation.org/user/">UseR!</a></p>
<p>Statisticians using multiple softwares (SAS, R, Python) will have found differences in analysis results that warrant further justification. Whilst some industries may accept results not being the same as long as they are “close”, the highly regulated pharmaceutical industry would require an identical match in results. Yet, discrepancies might still occur, and knowing the reasons (different methods, options, algorithms etc) is critical to the modern statistician and subsequent regulatory submissions.</p>
<p>In this talk I will introduce <strong>CAMIS: Comparing Analysis Method Implementations in Software</strong>. https://psiaims.github.io/CAMIS/ It is a joint-project between PHUSE, the R Validation Hub, PSI AIMS, R consortium and openstatsware. The aim of CAMIS is to investigate and document differences and similarities between different statistical softwares such as SAS and R. We use Quarto and Github to document methods, algorithms and comparisons between softwares through small case studies, and all articles are contributed by the community. In the transition from proprietary to open source technology in the industry, CAMIS can serve as a guidebook to navigate this process.</p>
<section id="keywords-cross-industry-collaboration-multi-lingua-open-source-quarto" class="level4">
<h4 class="anchored" data-anchor-id="keywords-cross-industry-collaboration-multi-lingua-open-source-quarto">keywords: cross industry collaboration, multi-lingua, open-source, quarto</h4>
<p><img src="https://kundan-kumarr.github.io/talks/community_20240710_camis/image_talk_20240710.png" class="img-fluid"></p>



</section>

 ]]></description>
  <category>Community</category>
  <guid>https://kundan-kumarr.github.io/talks/community_20240710_camis/</guid>
  <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  <media:content url="https://kundan-kumarr.github.io/talks/community_20240710_camis/image_talk_20240710.png" medium="image" type="image/png" height="80" width="144"/>
</item>
<item>
  <title>A one year recap on teaching statistcis to medical students: how can R and Quarto help?</title>
  <link>https://kundan-kumarr.github.io/talks/rstats_20240613_teaching/</link>
  <description><![CDATA[ 




<p><img src="https://kundan-kumarr.github.io/talks/rstats_20240613_teaching/image_talk_20240613.png" class="img-fluid"></p>
<p>Time and place: <strong>June 13 2024. Online</strong></p>
<p>Slides for this talk can be accessed <a href="https://github.com/chizapoth/talks/tree/master/2024-06-13-rmedicine" class="btn btn-success btn-sm">Code</a>.</p>
<section id="about-the-topic" class="level2">
<h2 class="anchored" data-anchor-id="about-the-topic">About the topic</h2>
<p>The Department of Biostatistics at University of Oslo offer statistics courses at different levels for medical students and PhD candidates with clinical backgrounds. The courses were traditionally taught with a focus on theory instead of data analysis, where SPSS and STATA were the tools of choice.</p>
<p>Since 2023 spring semester, we have been gradually transforming some of our statistics courses into R, using Quarto course websites and Carpentries style live-coding instruction. With new Quarto tools (such as WebR) we also added interactivity in the code blocks. So far we have transformed two courses with over 100 students who have almost no programming experience. We have observed impressive progress in the skill development, and received significantly more positive feedback when it comes to statistics education.</p>
<p>In this talk, I would like to share our experience on the successes and challenges throughout the process. Looking back, is it cost-effective? Definitely. Can we do better in the future? Almost surely. If you are also planning to adopt new technology in your teaching activities, join us to learn more about what you can do to make the transition happen!</p>
<p>Course website can be accessed <a href="https://ocbe-uio.github.io/teaching_mf9130e/">here</a></p>



</section>

 ]]></description>
  <category>Rstats</category>
  <category>Quarto</category>
  <category>Teaching</category>
  <guid>https://kundan-kumarr.github.io/talks/rstats_20240613_teaching/</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
  <title>Transforming medical statistics classroom with R and Quarto</title>
  <link>https://kundan-kumarr.github.io/talks/rstats_20230721_teaching/</link>
  <description><![CDATA[ 




<p><img src="https://kundan-kumarr.github.io/talks/rstats_20230721_teaching/image_talk_20230721.png" class="img-fluid"></p>
<p>Time and place: <strong>July 21, 2023 10AM. Roche office, Basel, Switzerland</strong></p>
<p>Slides for this talk can be accessed <a href="https://github.com/chizapoth/talks/tree/master/2023-07-21-basel" class="btn btn-success btn-sm">Code</a>.</p>
<section id="about-the-topic" class="level2">
<h2 class="anchored" data-anchor-id="about-the-topic">About the topic</h2>
<p>The 8 day introductory statistics course (MF9130) at the Faculty of Medicine, University of Oslo is designed for PhD students in medicine, biology, psychology and other health related fields. Similar to other conventional teaching methods, the course has been focusing largely on theory and hand calculation. The software has been Stata and SPSS, and data analysis was mostly left for the students to figure out on their own.</p>
<p>This year, we made an attempt to transform the course with R, and aimed to teach more practical data analysis skills. We added one session per day where the instructor guide students on R and project management, importing data , basic manipulation and statistical methods. The IT skills of the students vary greatly, and therefore we used the ‘sticky notes’ help system borrowed from the Carpentries to make sure everyone could get help in the first days. We have created a course website using Quarto, where all the material and R exercises (with rendered solution) are available for self-study. We have witnessed amazing progress - by the end of the first week, students with the least computer / data skills were able to work on dataframes, make basic plots and do a chi-squared test. This helps build students confidence in data and statistics, and as a result, they can start to work on their own datasets using the skills immediately.</p>



</section>

 ]]></description>
  <category>Rstats</category>
  <category>Quarto</category>
  <category>Teaching</category>
  <guid>https://kundan-kumarr.github.io/talks/rstats_20230721_teaching/</guid>
  <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
  <title>My Dummy Talk</title>
  <link>https://kundan-kumarr.github.io/talks/dummy_talk/</link>
  <description><![CDATA[ 




<p>This is a simple demo of a Quarto talk listing with an image, title, and subtitle.</p>




 ]]></description>
  <guid>https://kundan-kumarr.github.io/talks/dummy_talk/</guid>
  <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  <media:content url="https://kundan-kumarr.github.io/talks/dummy_talk/talk_image.png" medium="image" type="image/png" height="80" width="144"/>
</item>
<item>
  <title>Public health surveillance and reporting</title>
  <link>https://kundan-kumarr.github.io/talks/ph_20230330_sp/</link>
  <description><![CDATA[ 




<p><img src="https://kundan-kumarr.github.io/talks/ph_20230330_sp/image_talk_20230330.png" class="img-fluid"></p>
<p>Time and place: <strong>Mar.&nbsp;30, 2023 12:00 PM–1:00 PM</strong></p>
<p>Hybrid: <strong>Georg Sverdrups hus and Zoom</strong></p>
<p><a href="https://www.ub.uio.no/english/courses-events/events/open-science-lunch/2023-03-30.html">Event page</a></p>
<section id="about-the-topic" class="level2">
<h2 class="anchored" data-anchor-id="about-the-topic">About the topic</h2>
<p>Situational awareness is key to fast response during a public health emergency, such as COVID-19 pandemic. However, making disease surveillance reports that cover different geographical units for various metrics and data registries is both resource intensive and time consuming. Open source tools such as R packages, GitHub and Airflow can make this process automatic, reproducible and scalable.</p>
<p>Every day during the pandemic, Sykdomspulsen team at the Norwegian Institute of Public Health (FHI/NIPH) fetched data from more than 15 data sources, cleaned, censored datasets and carried out a wide range of statistical analyses. Over 1000 situational reports containing automated graphs and tables were produced before breakfast time.</p>
<p>Grab you matpakke and join us for a presentation from Chi Zhang about how Sykdomspulsen team used and developed open source software to make public health surveillance and reporting more efficient, followed up by a discussion on the benefits and concerns of making these data public. We will end with an open Q&amp;A session as usual!</p>



</section>

 ]]></description>
  <category>ph</category>
  <guid>https://kundan-kumarr.github.io/talks/ph_20230330_sp/</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
  <title>Machine Learning in Intensive Care Units</title>
  <link>https://kundan-kumarr.github.io/talks/ehr_20221013_ml_icu/</link>
  <description><![CDATA[ 




<p>A 45 minutes trial lecture to fulfill the requirement of my PhD degree.</p>
<p><img src="https://kundan-kumarr.github.io/talks/ehr_20221013_ml_icu/image_talk_20221013.png" class="img-fluid"></p>




 ]]></description>
  <category>RWD-EHR</category>
  <guid>https://kundan-kumarr.github.io/talks/ehr_20221013_ml_icu/</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
  <title>Network Analysis of Hospital EHR data</title>
  <link>https://kundan-kumarr.github.io/talks/ehr_20210218_biday/</link>
  <description><![CDATA[ 




<p><img src="https://kundan-kumarr.github.io/talks/ehr_20210218_biday/image_ehr_20210218.png" class="img-fluid"></p>
<p>Since this post doesn’t specify an explicit <code>image</code>, the first image in the post will be used in the listing page of posts.</p>




 ]]></description>
  <category>RWD-EHR</category>
  <guid>https://kundan-kumarr.github.io/talks/ehr_20210218_biday/</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2021 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
  <title>Learning from Hospital EHR data with R</title>
  <link>https://kundan-kumarr.github.io/talks/ehr_20191028_rladies/</link>
  <description><![CDATA[ 




<p><img src="https://kundan-kumarr.github.io/talks/ehr_20191028_rladies/image_ehr_20191028.png" class="img-fluid"></p>




 ]]></description>
  <category>ehr</category>
  <guid>https://kundan-kumarr.github.io/talks/ehr_20191028_rladies/</guid>
  <pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2019 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
  <title>Building Website in R: Step by Step Introduction to blogdown</title>
  <link>https://kundan-kumarr.github.io/talks/rstats_20190402_blogdown/</link>
  <description><![CDATA[ 




<p><img src="https://kundan-kumarr.github.io/talks/rstats_20190402_blogdown/image_rstats_20190402.png" class="img-fluid"></p>
<p>Since this post doesn’t specify an explicit <code>image</code>, the first image in the post will be used in the listing page of posts.</p>




 ]]></description>
  <category>rstats</category>
  <guid>https://kundan-kumarr.github.io/talks/rstats_20190402_blogdown/</guid>
  <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
